<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KsharSutra</string>
    <string name="emailID">abc@example.com</string>
    <string name="phoneno">9876543210</string>
    <string name="address">Kshara Sutra Hospital, near N.L. High School, Malad West, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400064</string>
    <string name="book_an_appointment">Book an appointment</string>
    <string name="piles_description">Swollen rectal veins causing discomfort, itching, and bleeding, often due to straining during bowel movements.</string>
    <string name="fissure_description">A painful tear in the anal lining, causing discomfort and bleeding during bowel movements.</string>
    <string name="PilonidalSinus_description">A small tunnel-like cavity in the skin, often near the tailbone, prone to infection.</string>
    <string name="fistula_description">An abnormal tunnel between the anal canal and the skin near the anus, often due to an untreated abscess.</string>
    <string name="learn_more">Learn More</string>
    <string name="precautions_label">Precautions</string>
    <string name="treatment_label">Treatment</string>
    <string name="piles_treatment">
        <![CDATA[
        • <b>Dietary changes</b>: Increase fiber intake to soften stools and prevent straining.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Topical treatments</b>: Use over-the-counter creams, ointments, or suppositories to reduce pain, itching, and inflammation.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Sclerotherapy or banding</b>: In-office procedures to shrink hemorrhoids by cutting off their blood supply.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Rubber band ligation</b>: Place a rubber band around the base of the hemorrhoid to cut off its blood supply, causing it to shrink and fall off.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Hemorrhoidectomy</b>: Surgical removal of hemorrhoids for severe cases unresponsive to other treatments.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="piles_precautions">
        <![CDATA[
        • <b>Eat high-fiber foods</b>: To soften stools.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Stay hydrated and exercise regularly</b>.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Avoid prolonged sitting or standing</b>: Take breaks.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Use gentle, fragrance-free wipes Or soft toilet paper.</b>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="fissure_treatment">
        <![CDATA[
        • <b>Topical ointments or creams</b>: Over-the-counter or prescription creams containing calcium channel blockers or nitroglycerin to relax the anal sphincter and promote healing.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Sitz baths</b>: Soak the anal area in warm water for 10-15 minutes several times a day to relieve pain and promote healing.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Dietary changes</b>: Increase fiber intake and drink plenty of water to soften stools and reduce strain during bowel movements.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Botulinum toxin injection</b>: Injections into the anal sphincter to relax the muscle and promote healing in chronic fissures.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Surgical sphincterotomy</b>: In severe or chronic cases, a surgical procedure to cut the internal anal sphincter muscle to reduce spasm and promote healing.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="fissure_precautions">
        <![CDATA[
        • <b>Maintain a high-fiber diet</b>: And drink plenty of water to prevent constipation.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Practice good anal hygiene</b>: Avoid excessive wiping or harsh cleansers.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Use stool softeners or topical ointments</b>: As recommended by a healthcare professional to promote healing.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Avoid straining during bowel movements</b>: Consider using a stool or footstool to elevate your feet while on the toilet to ease passage.<br/>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="pilonidalsinus_treatment">
        <![CDATA[
        • <b>Incision and drainage</b>: If the sinus is infected, a healthcare provider may need to make an incision to drain pus and debris from the abscess.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Antibiotics</b>: In cases of infection, antibiotics may be prescribed to treat the bacterial infection.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Laser hair removal or shaving</b>: To prevent recurrence, hair removal methods may be used to reduce hair in the affected area.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Surgical excision</b>: For recurrent or chronic cases, surgical removal of the sinus tract and surrounding tissue may be necessary.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="doctor_image">Doctor Image</string>


    <string name="pilonidalsinus_precautions">
        <![CDATA[
        • <b>Maintain good hygiene</b>: Especially in the buttock area.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Keep the area clean and dry</b>: To prevent bacterial growth.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Avoid prolonged sitting</b>: Or pressure on the affected area.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Seek medical attention</b>: If symptoms persist or worsen.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="fistula_treatment">
        <![CDATA[
        • <b>Incision and Drainage</b>: Drain the abscess surgically to relieve pain and prevent further infection.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Seton Placement</b>: Insert a thread-like material into the fistula tract to keep it open and allow for continuous drainage.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Fistulotomy</b>: Cut open the entire length of the fistula tract to remove it completely.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Fistulectomy</b>: Surgically remove the entire fistula tract, possibly including surrounding tissue.<br/><br/>
        • <b>LIFT Procedure</b>: Identify and ligate the internal opening of the fistula tract while preserving the anal sphincter muscles.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Advancement Flap Repair</b>: Use tissue from the inside of the rectum to cover and close the internal opening of the fistula.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Fibrin Glue Injection</b>: Inject fibrin glue into the fistula tract to seal it off and promote healing.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Biological Plugs</b>: Use biological plugs made from materials such as porcine collagen to seal the internal opening of the fistula.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Antibiotics</b>: Prescribe antibiotics to treat or prevent infection.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="fistula_precautions">
        <![CDATA[
        • <b>Maintain good anal hygiene</b>: Keep the area clean and dry to prevent infection and irritation.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Avoid prolonged sitting</b>: Or pressure on the anal region to reduce discomfort and prevent exacerbation of symptoms.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Seek medical attention</b>: If you experience persistent pain, swelling, or drainage from an opening near the anus.<br/><br/>
        • <b>Follow healthcare provider recommendations</b>: For treatment, which may include antibiotics, surgical drainage, or surgical removal of the fistula tract.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="edit_profile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="clinic_timing">Monday - Saturday\n10:00 am - 1:00 pm \n04:30 pm - 06:00 pm</string>
</resources>